As the evangelists continue to minister the anointing water to the congregation
the darkness in this woman's life was exposed by the light of God.
Try though it might, the demonic entity in her life could not withstand the power and armour of God,
working through the anointing water.
The Anointing Water Revival - Birmingham, UK
The woman was escorted to the front so that all could witness the power of Jesus' triumph
over the power of the devil in her life.
The battle between light and darkness was evident in the life of this woman,
as every chain that an enemy had used to draw her back was being broken, in the name above all names.
Watch how she received her freedom.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ! You evil spirit - it's time for you to speak out - who are you?
You say what?
There are many of us.
How many?
Many.
You must speak. How many?
Forty.
Begin to name yourselves. Who is number one?
Madness.
What is the meaning of that?
I destroyed her brain and made her go crazy.
I made her mad.
Who is number two?
I still want to speak.
Speak out. What have you done to her, madness?
She sees a psychiatrist, right now.
I wanted them to lock her up for life.
Why do you want them to lock her up for life?
Because I have tried to kill her; she won’t die. I tried to make her kill herself.
How did you try to make her kill herself?
She overdoses – tablets.
I have told her to jump off buildings.
She won’t. She prays, that is the problem.
Someone keeps on protecting her.
Who keeps protecting her?
You know who it is.
Who? Tell us.
I’m not telling you.
I will not utter that name.
Which name?
But it's the name she prays to.
You know the name.
Don't ask me.
Who is number two?
Lust, seduction.
How many powers do you have in her body?
Many.
Where are the powers in her body?
You spirit of lust and seduction - where are the powers in her body?
In her hips.
Explain the power in her hips
And in her breasts.
You said you had power in her hips and in her breasts. Explain the power in her hips!
I came in after her father abused her.
So, that was how I came in.
I said - the power in her hips - how does she use the power in her hips?
She doesn’t have to do much. She only has to stand there and men come to her.
So, once men see her hips, they are attracted to her?
That’s right. They just use her.
She doesn’t have any power except in her hips for men to destroy her.
They use her. I made them use her.
And then, that’s when it hurts and then she goes crazy.
That’s what I want. I want her to go crazy and lose her mind.
How do you use her as a spirit of lust?
Get off me. Leave me alone. Let me go.
I said, what do you use her to do as a spirit of lust. What are the things she does as a spirit of lust?
How does it push her?
That lust makes her live in sin.
No matter how hard she tries, if she has lust, then she is still living in sin.
You mean that anyone who is living in sin and in lust - you can operate in them?
Yes.
You demon, right now it is your time to leave this body.
You've made the greatest mistake by allowing her to come here.
However many you are, Jesus Christ is more than you.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ - it is your time to leave, in Jesus' name!
Come out of this body, and set her free!
Come out of her in Jesus' name!
Everything not of Jesus Christ - come out!
You have no place in this body. She belongs to Jesus Christ.
This anointing water is sent by Prophet T.B. Joshua. You must leave.
Whether you like it or not, you must go.
You are going to where Jesus wants you to go, but you must leave her! Come out!
Come out of her! Out!
You must leave. Get out of this body! Get out! Leave her alone! Go, in Jesus' name!
Deliverance Through the Anointing Water, in Jesus' Name
They are calling the name I don't want to hear.
Come out!
Deliverance Through the Anointing Water, in Jesus' Name
In Jesus' mighty name!
♪ Blood of Jesus
The blood of Jesus set me free
From sin and sorrow
Oh God, my life spent with you ♪
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ - you are declared free in Jesus' name! Rise to your feet.
Set Free Through the Anointing Water, in Jesus' Name
How are you, sister?
How are you?
I am OK, thanks.
I am just a bit dazed.
What just happened to you? Do you know what you were saying just now?
Not really. All I know is I felt the spray and from there, something came over me.
And right now - how are you feeling?
I feel at peace right now, with myself.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Sister, you are declared free.
Go and live your life to follow Jesus and walk in the light of your testimony.
Thank you, so much!
I have suffered so much and it is good to know that I am free now!
Thank You, Jesus!
ANOINTING WATER REVIVAL IN BIRMINGHAM, UNITED KINGDOM
ANOINTING WATER REVIVAL - TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Charlene. I am from Leicester - UK, originally born in Zimbabwe.
What was the problem that brought you to the Anointing Water Revival in Birmingham today?
I had constant torment, depression, chronic pain and sickness all the time.
I was in and out of the hospital with different illnesses, including mental health issues as well.
Can you explain the mental health issue you were having before?
Before – I had several issues - the impulse to cut myself, self-harm, suicide attempts.
I made several suicide attempts – overdoses and attempts like that.
Nasty stuff.
You said that you had suicidal thoughts, and you attempted suicide several times. Is that right?
Yes, that is right.
Constantly, I heard a voice telling me to kill myself. It nagged me.
If I was driving, it would say, “Drive into this wall”
or, “Go, jump off that building; you don’t deserve to live”.
It was a very negative voice.
Have you ever been hospitalized because of this problem?
Yes, I have.
I have been hospitalized, and I have seen a psychiatrist.
They tried their best in terms of treating me with medication.
I was on all the medication I needed to be on.
The medication and treatment - had that been able to put an end to the mental problem you were having?
No, not an end.
It just elevated my mood a bit.
It makes you feel a bit better.
It is just like a ...
The anti-psychotics worked really only for my mood but the problem didn't go away.
You mentioned that you made several suicide attempts.
Have you ever been hospitalized as a result of this?
Yes, many times.
I had been on life support in the past.
I had been in a coma because I attempted suicide.
I had to have my stomach pumped for the drugs to be taken out.
I was in hospital a couple of times, more than four times due to suicide attempts.
The last time was the worst.
I took about 60 tablets, 60 Tramadols.
I had a test that climbed to the scale of 3, which means I was clinically dead.
I was on life support and in a coma for a few days.
The doctors really thought I would die.
They left me on life support thinking that was it, they should just leave me
because I had stopped breathing for a few hours and they thought I would be brain-dead.
But somehow – it was God, really – I woke up.
A lot of people just die from brain damage but I woke up and I thank God for that.
They were shocked as well.
Amen. You said you were in a coma and on life support, you were clinically dead
but by the grace of God you came out of it. Is that right?
Yes, I did.
Is this what prompted you to seek for a solution from God Almighty?
I had always been a praying person but every time I tried to, there was a pattern.
Every time I tried to make my life right with God, I would get spiritual attacks.
I mean they are not just a ...
They had become physical as well.
One time, I got scratched in my eyes and couldn’t see for 48 hours.
Physical things like being thrown constantly around my room or my bed.
It was always a pattern.
When I started going to church and trying to live according to God’s will,
there were always issues that would come up.
I would start getting spiritual attacks, particularly with sickness.
What was it that was scratching your eyes and causing you to be thrown around the room?
It wasn’t just me; I have a sister as well. She got thrown up and down by it.
She called it a creature with goat’s legs and a weird face.
Could you see this creature?
I saw a shadow of it many times but she saw it.
But always, I felt it and it clawed me in my eyes.
Alright. You came to the Anointing Water Revival today with these challenges.
Can you tell us what happened when the Anointing Water was ministered to you?
When the Anointing Water was ministered, it felt stinging.
I just felt a sting and I felt like turning my head away.
I felt like leaving, like running away, basically.
I don’t know – that was not me because I was OK.
Something just came over me.
How did you feel at that time when the Anointing Water was being ministered to you?
It felt as if I was being stung by something; I just didn’t like it.
I wanted to go. It was as if something came over me; I wasn’t myself.
I was there but there was something inside of me that didn't like the Anointing Water.
At the end of the prayer - tell us what happened and how were you feeling.
After I came to back to my senses, I felt very light.
I feel like something has come out of me from deep inside.
I feel fresh air and that I can breathe now.
I actually enjoy breathing because it feels so good; praise God!
What do you believe Jesus Christ has done for you through the medium of the Anointing Water?
I believe Jesus Christ has shown immeasurable mercy to me
because of what I have been going through.
I have cried and cried in bed, asking Jesus why all that was happening to me all the time.
I would even say to Him, “I am so tired; I can’t wake up every morning like this”.
I would say to Him, “I know that suicide is a sin; I don’t want to go to hell.
If I die, I want to go and be with You, Jesus”. He answered my prayers.
Amen. Yes, the prayers of many years are not lost.
We thank God Almighty today for meeting you at the point of your need.
We thank God for shining the light of His life into your spirit, soul and body
and dispelling every shade of darkness in your spirit, in your soul, in your mind and in your body.
We encourage you to maintain this wonderful deliverance and a new life in Christ Jesus
by making God's Word the standard for your thoughts, your words, and your actions,
and it shall be well with you, day by day and hour by hour, till we are glorified at last in Jesus' name.
Amen. Thank You, Jesus!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons, and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.